Guide to the Cornell United Religious Work records, 1869-1972,
Cornell United Religious Work records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell United Religious Work records, 1869-1972, 1965-1972 (bulk)
39-2-1468
Cornell United Religious Work.
34.5 cubic ft.
Correspondence, Manuscripts,Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications, Scrapbooks
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of the Cornell University Christian Association.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of the Cornell University Christian Association include minutes of the Board of Directors, business meetings, the Executive Committee, and other committees; constitution and bylaws; officers and members; financial records; scrapbooks; and office files of Richard Henry Edwards, Director. Records of Cornell United Religious Work include minutes of the Board of Control; office files of Richard H. Edwards, Director, 1930-1939, James A. G. Moore, Acting Director, 1937-1939, and William W. Mendenhall, 1939-1943; scrapbooks; and correspondence relating to the functions and activities of CURW, 1932-1933. Also, tape recordings of the National Association of College Chaplains Conference, 1965; portraits; memorabilia; and miscellaneous reports, books, clippings, pamphlets, photograph albums, and periodicals relating to CURW activities.
Includes records of the East Harlem Project (1965-68), POWER Project files (1968), and the Cornell in Central America Project (1953-1969).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell United Religious Work.; Edwards, Richard Henry, 1877-1954.; Mendenhall, William W.; Moore, James A. G.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Religion.; Cornell University Christian Association.; National Association of College Chaplains.
Subjects:
Universities and colleges--Religion.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.)--Religious life and customs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Collections #39-2-1267 and #39-2-1268 are restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
NOTES
Includes collection #39-2-1267, 39-2-1268 and 39-2-1604.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I
  - United Christian Works at Cornell, 1919-1922 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Treman Endowment, 1922-1924 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CUCA Trustee Minutes, 1887-1908 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1907-1910 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Finance Committee, 1923-24 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1947-48 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1946-47 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1945-46 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1944-45 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1943-44 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1942-43 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board of Control, 1941-42 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1938-41 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Minutes of Board of Control of CURW, 1939-40 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Minutes of the Meetings of the Board of Control, 1938-39 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board of Control Minutes, 1937-38 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's Section of Board of Control (records and minutes), 1937-38 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board of Control Men's Section, 1936-37 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Full Board of Control, 1936-37 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board of Control (includes men's section), 1935-36 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board of Control Minutes of Men's Discussion, 1935-36 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board of Control, 1932-33 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board of Control, 1931-32 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Minutes of Board of Control, 1930-31 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board of Control, 1930-31 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board of Control, records, minutes, 1928-29 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - CUCA Board, 1927-28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - CUCA Board, 1926-27 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - CUCA, 1925-26 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board of Directors CUCA, 1924-25 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board of Control Minutes of CUCA Cabinet, 1921-22 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - CUCA minutes of board of control, 1920-21 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - CUCA minutes board of control, 1919-20 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - CUCA trustees minutes, 1908-14 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - CUCA trustee minutes, 1887-1906 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - CACU board of trustees, 1887-1930 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CACU records, 1930-38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - CUCA trustee records, 1887-1905 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Officers of CACU, 1869-1902 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Officers of Christian Association, 1877-1921 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Executive committee reports, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Weds Prayer Meeting, 1895-1896 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Women's Band, 1889-1897 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Constitutions, 1876, 1903, 1906, 1921 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Executive Committee, 1890-1896 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Finance Committee, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Soph and jr Class Prayer meeting, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Prayer meeting, 1897 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Library committee, 18997-1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Committee reports, 1905-1906 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Program Outline, 1905-06 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Manuals, Pre-1952 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Constitution of CURW, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting CURW, 1943-52 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Report Letters, 1890-1903 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Records of the Cornell Christian Association, 1901-02 (Box 2, Volume 1)
  - Records, No Date (Box 2, Volume 2)
  - CUCA, 1888-1898 (Box 2, Volume 3)
  - Bible study committee, 1891-97 (Box 2, Volume 4)
  - Sunday committee, 1888-90 (Box 2, Volume 5)
  - Tuesday invitation committee, 1888-90 (Box 2, Volume 6)
  - Invitation committee, 1890 (Box 2, Volume 7)
  - Invitation committee, 1991 (Box 2, Volume 8)
  - CUCA Committee, 1888-90 (Box 2, Volume 9)
  - Music Committee, 1888-89 (Box 2, Volume 10)
  - Topics and Leaders, 1991 (Box 2, Volume 11)
  - CUCA Membership committee, 1888-91 (Box 2, Volume 12)
  - Membership list, 1888-89 (Box 2, Volume 13)
  - Treasurer's List, 1893-94 (Box 2, Volume 14)
  - CUCA membership list, 1889-90 (Box 2, Volume 15)
  - Principal Helps for CUCA, 1890-91 (Box 2, Volume 16)
  - CUCA, 1895-1909 (Box 2, Volume 17)
  - CU Mission Band of Volunteers, 1887-1912 (Box 2, Volume 18)
  - Record of Members of CU Mission Band of Volunteers, 1891-97 (Box 2, Volume 19)
  - Cornell total abstinence league, 1888-92 (Box 2, Volume 20)
  - Minutes Pr meeting, 1896-97 (Box 2, Volume 21)
  - Minutes Bible study com., 1896 (Box 2, Volume 22)
  - Minutes Neighborhood Com, 1896 (Box 2, Volume 23)
  - Minutes of Membership committee, 1896 (Box 2, Volume 24)
  - CUCA finances, 1903-04 (Box 3, Volume 1)
  - CUCA cash book, 1905-08 (Box 3, Volume 2)
  - CUCA cash book, 1908-10 (Box 3, Volume 3)
  - CUCA cash book, 1910-12 (Box 3, Volume 4)
  - CUCA cash book, 1900-04 (Box 3, Volume 5)
  - Accounts, 1894-1903 (Box 3, Volume 6)
  - Ledger, 1900s (Box 3, Volume 7)
  - Financial Statement, 1887 (Box 3, Volume 8)
  - Receipts and Expenditures, 1911-12 (Box 3, Volume 9)
  - Receipts, 1895-1901 (Box 3, Volume 10)
  - File titles and cross reference list, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Application file, Up to 1929 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Areopagus, Up to 1929 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Barnes Hall (renovation and repair, contracts, use of building), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of control, full, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of trustees, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Clubs CURW, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CURW Finances, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Endowment, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cornell co-op, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Conferences (national, state, and university), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Constituent groups and staff members, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Cornellian council, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - CURW Criticisms, plans, summaries, annual meetings, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Employment Bursar, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Finance Circular letters, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Financial statements, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Finance, names of possible large donors, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Forum, CURW and voluntary courses, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Library, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Freshman camp, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Freshman desk book (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Kitchen, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Men's cabinet (includes student lecture bureau), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - NYA students, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Office, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Peace action, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Publicity, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Recommendation letters, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Residence, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - ROTC (military training), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Rural Institute, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Sage chapel, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Social Service work, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Student council, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Student joint board, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Student loan fund, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Town and county ministers assns, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Universities, data on other, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Vocations, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Women's cabinet, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Women's work, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Worship (Holy week, special services, etc), 1929 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - YMCA, YWCA, and SCM, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Areopagus, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Application file, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Barnes hall (renovation and repair, contracts, use of building), 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board of Control, full, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Cabin, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Clubs CURW, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Conferences, CURW, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Constituent groups and staff members, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Employment Bureau, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Endowment, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Finance, Circular Letters, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Financial Statements, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Freshman Camp, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Freshman desk book, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Forum, CURW, voluntary courses, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kitchen, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Library, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Conferences (National, state and university), 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cornellian Council, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Cornell Co-op, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - CURW (CUCA) criticisms, plans, summaries, annual meetings, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Men's Cabinet (Includes student lecture bureau), 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - NYA Students, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Office, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Peace action, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Publicity (Barnes hall bulletin, CURW review, etc), 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Recommendation letters, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Resilience, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - ROTC (Military training), 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rural Institute, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Sage chapel, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Social service work, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Student Council, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Student Joint Board, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Student Loan Fund, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Town and Country Ministers Assns, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Universities, data on other, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Vocations, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Women's Cabinet, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - YMCA, YWCA, SCM, 1930-34 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Aeropagus, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Application File, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Barnes Hall (Renovation and repair, contracts, use of building), 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board of control, full, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board of trustees, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cabin, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Clubs CURW, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Conference, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cornell co-op, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Cornellian council, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conferences, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Constituent groups and staff members, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - CURW, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lists of sections of CURW, 1937-38 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Employment Bureau, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Endowment, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Finance, circular letters, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Forum CURW and volunteer courses, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Freshman camp, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Freshman desk book, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Kitchen, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Library, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Misc, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Men's Cabinet, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - NYA Students, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Office, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Peace action, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Publicity, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Residence, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - ROTC, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Rural Institute, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Sage Chapel, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Social Service Work, 1935-39 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Student Board, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Student Council, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Student loan fund, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Student lecture bureau, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Chapel, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Town and county ministers assns, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Universities, data on other, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Vocations, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Cabinet, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Women's work, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - YMCA, YWCA, SCM, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Worship, 1935-39 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Finance alumni fund, 1937-38 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rural Institute - CURW Extension, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Men's Council, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Student Lecture Bureau, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Special Service Work, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Women's Council, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Missionary school - Summer School of Christian Education, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Student Board, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Finance Campaign Alumni Faculty, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Campus forum series, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Publicity, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Student Christian IVT, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - German Refugee Fund, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Christian Summer Fellowship, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Board of Control, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - File titles and cross reference list, 1938-39 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Conferences, CURW, 1940-41 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Barnes Hall, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Conferences, 1941-42 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - CURW annual banquet, 1941-43 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - CURW Criticisms, plans, summaries, annual meetings, 1938-43 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Financial statements, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Finance, circular letters, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Finance contribution record, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Forum series, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Freshman camp, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Freshman Desk Book, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Graduate group, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Janitors, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Men's camp, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Publicity, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Sage chapel, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Student board, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Women's cabinet, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Worship (Holy week, special services), 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - YMCA, YWCA, SCM, 1940-43 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Directory of the University, 1942-43 (Box 7, Volume 1)
  - Directory of the University, 1943-44 (Box 7, Volume 2)
  - Directory of the University, 1944-45 (Box 7, Volume 3)
  - Directory of the University, 1946 (Box 7, Volume 4)
  - Directory of the University, 1947 (Box 7, Volume 5)
  - Directory of the University, 1948 (Box 7, Volume 6)
  - Directory of the University, 1948-49 (Box 7, Volume 7)
  - Directory of the University, 1949-50 (Box 7, Volume 8)
  - Directory of the University, 1950-51 (Box 7, Volume 9)
  - Scrapbook, 1889-90 (Box 8, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1901-05 (Box 8, Volume 2)
  - Newspaper Scrapbook, 1916 (Box 8, Volume 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1885-1900 (Box 8, Volume 4)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1919-1923 (Box 9, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1923-1925 (Box 9, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1928-30 (Box 10, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1930s (Box 10, Volume 2)
  - Cornell Women's Religious Association Activities scrapbook, 1931-33 (Box 11, Volume 1)
  - CURW women's council scrapbook, 1934-36 (Box 11, Volume 1)
  - CURW scrap book, 1937-38 (Box 11, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1933-36 (Box 11, Volume 3)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1925-28 (Box 13, Volume 1)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1942-46 (Box 13, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1946-47 (Box 13, Volume 3)
  - William Rogers/Brazil, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence with Pope Pius and President Truman, 1946-49 (Box 14, Volume 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1940s (Box 14, Volume 3)
  - Gods of the Campus, 1949 (Box 14, Volume 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1963 (Box 14, Volume 5)
  - Paul Gibbons/Harlem, 1966 (Box 14, Volume 6)
  - Richard Bausman/Baptist, 1971 (Box 14, Volume 7)
  - The Ark, 1969 (Box 14, Volume 8)
  - Hollis Hayward/Methodist, 1972 (Box 14, Volume 9)
  - Paul Gibbons/Cornell Power Plant, 1968 (Box 14, Volume 10)
  - Paul Gibbons/New Community, 1972 (Box 14, Volume 11)
  - CURW brochure, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Material for committee report, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - CURW committee correspondence, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - CURW history and general, 1932-37 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Cornell religious work data, 1924-37 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - CURW, 1919-37 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Edwards inquiry, 1932-33 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - California UCLA, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Syracuse, 1930-33 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Problems submitted to the special committee, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - CURW general material, 1932-34 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Yale, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Wisconsin, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Mass state, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Missouri, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Miami, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Pennsylvania, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Princeton, 1933 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Iowa, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Harvard, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Illinois, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Abbey, Merrill R, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Adams, James L, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Agus, Jacob, 1960s (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Ahmad, Anis, 1960s (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - al-Faruqi, Isma'il, 1960s (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alexander, John, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Alves, Ruben, 1974-75 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, Benjamin, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Andrews, Charles, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Ahmad, Eqbal, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Armstrong, A James, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Arroyo, Ciriaco, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Ashbrook, James B, 1967-68 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Averill, Lloyd, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Bamberger, Bernard J, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Barr, Browne, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Barr, Orlando Sydney, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Barth, Markus, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Bartlett, Gene, 1960-64 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Baum, Gregory, 1967-72 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bayne, Stephen Jr, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Beach, Waldo, 1968-69 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Beaven, Robert, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Becker, Sherwood B, 1966-67 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Bennett, John, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Bennett, Thomas, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Berrigan, Daniel, 1973-75 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Berry, Donald, 1961-62 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Bertocci, Peter, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Blake, Eugene Carson, 1963-71 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Blanchard, Roger, 1961-63 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Bloy, Myron B, Jr, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Boddie, Charles, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Bonthius, Robert, 1957-58 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Bordelon, Marvin, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Borowitz, Rabbi Eugene, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Bosley, Harold, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Boyd, Malcolm, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Brickner, Balfour, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Robert McAfee, 1961-75 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Burtchaell, James T, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Burtness, James, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Bushman, Richard L, 1975-78 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Buttrick, George A, 1959-66 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Calhoun, Robert, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Campbell, Ernest T, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Carlebach, Shlomo, 1973-74 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Carmines, Alvin A, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Carothers, J Edward, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Carroll, Elizabeth, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Carse, James P, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Case, Harold C, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Catchings, L Maynard, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Cleage, Albert B, Jr, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Christensen, Joseph, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Clowney, Edmund P, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Cleary, Msgr Donald M, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Clements, Rex, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Climenhaga, Arthur M, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Cobb, John B Jr, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Coburn, John B, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Coffin, William S Jr, 1965-79 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Cohen, Arthur A, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Cole, Ned, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Collingwood, G Harris, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Cone, James H, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Contos, Leonidas, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Copenhaver, Charles L, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Corrigan, Daniel J, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Cox, Harvey G, 1963-67 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Cramton, Roger C, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Crane, Henry Hitt, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Crocker, John, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Cuninggim, Merrimon, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Cushman, Robert E, 1956-59 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Davidson, Carter, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Demarsh, Roy G, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Denton, Robert C, 1955-56 (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Devadutt, VE, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Davis, Joseph M, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Davis, Saville R, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Diamond, Malcolm L, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - DiGiacomo, James J, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Ditzen, Lowell R, 1962-63 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Doan, Gilbert E Jr, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Docherty, George M, 1957-61 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Douglass, Truman B, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Duffey, Joseph, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Elliot, Elisabeth, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Elliot, Ralph H, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Elson, Edward LR, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Falcone, Sebastian A, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Farley, Margaret A, RSM, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Faulkner, William, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Ferm, Deane W, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Ferre, Nels FS, 1959-60 (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Ferris, Theodore P, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Fink, Joseph, L, 1956-57 (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Finley, Donald H, 1955-58 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Fisher, Wallace, 1963-64 (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Fiske, Edward, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Flanagan, Ross, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Fletcher, John C, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Fletcher, Joseph, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Fowler, James W III, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Fry, Franklin C, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 106)
  - Fry, John R, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 107)
  - Gaebler, Max, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 108)
  - Gajardo, Joel, 1974-76 (Box 16, Folder 109)
  - Gandy, Samuel L, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 110)
  - Garrett, John, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 111)